Can you show me Well, the corridor or there the
Можешь мне показать Ну коридор или там
wife was sleeping there the wife was sleeping Show the wife was
жена спали там жена спали Покажи жена
sleeping Well, on the sly Well, on the sly
спали Ну втихаря Ну втихаря
Can you walk show Can you walk
Можешь пройтись показать Можешь пройтись
show Hello, hello, hello
показать Здравствуйте здравствуйте
I am from the city of Khmelnitsky in the city of
здравствуйте Я из города Хмельницкий в
Khmelnitsky in Samara Russia I see
города Хмельницкий в Самара Росси я вижу
Russia by the teeth Yes Samara Uta Yes samata by the
Россия по зубам Да Самару Ута Да
teeth Yes yes Well, well
самата по зубам Да
done you are a
да Ну ну молодец ты
comedian a comedian a comedian Yes, well done I
юморист юморист юморист Да молодец я
congratulate you And what do you communicate from
тебя поздравляю А чем общаетесь из
Samara from Samara Well, you know different
Самары из Самары Ну ты знаешь разные
topics whatever your heart desires
темы что твоей душе
I look
угодно я смотрите
from put up their apartments can you
из ставляют свои квартиры можете
show How is your
показать Как обустроена ваша
apartment arranged my wife is sleeping my wife don't
квартира у меня жена спит жену не
show me the apartment until
показывайте квартиру пока
I turn on the apartment I
квартиру я включу Свет я
will get the light how much life do you have life from
получу сколько ты жизни
your
жиз своей
wife Let's turn on the light on the sly let's turn on the light in your face Come on
жены Давай в тихаря включим свет в харя
let's go Well, how can I
включим свет Давай давай Ну как тебе
tell you She's in another room she's in another
сказать Она же в другой комнате она в
room I generally I generally
другой комнате я вообще я вообще в
hid in the far room That is, you are in the
дальнюю комнату спрятался То есть ты в
far room Turn on the light Show Turn
дальней комнате Включи свет Покажи
it off I get up  wait
Выключи встаю подожди
Oh that's cool show me that's cool show me come
О прикольно показывай прикольно
on Twist Show me the shelf floor Here's the door do you have
Покрути Покажи полка пол Вот дверь у вас
laminate or parquet what do you have and the bag what do you have
ламинат или паркет что у васна и пакет
there Yeah laminate laminate Yes
что у вас там Ага ламинат ламинат Да
look and if you can show me Well the
смотри а если можешь мне показать Ну
hallway or is there a wife a spa is a spa
коридор или там жена спа же спа
on the sly on
втихаря в
the sly Can you walk over and show me Can you walk over and show me No I
тихаря Можешь пройтись показать Можешь
can't go
пройтись показать Да не могу
any further Five steps over there come on
дальше Пять шагов туда
Here I'm already in the room
прой давай Вот тут я в комнате уже
Postol there's very little here I'm
Постол тут очень мало всего мне
interested in how the layouts are
интересно как планировки
p they just tell us that Russians do
п просто нам рассказывают что у русских
n't have toilets but I don't believe it Are
нет унитазов но я не верю в
you
это Ты
from nowhere is it really he flushes
что от не где они это реально он сливает
or is this a mock-up and this is a mock-up a
или это макет и это
Water water Show me water Water
макет а Воду воду Покажите воду Воду
water Show me Well you did
воду Покажите Ну вы
n't flush it
не я спустил
But I just saw a guy showing me that
А я просто видел мне чувак показывал что
it's like a fountain it's not
это как фонтанчик он не к канализации не
connected to the sewer not connected to the sewer what is a
подключенный канализации не подключенный
real toilet a real toilet Well
реальный унитаз реальный унитаз Ну
yeah and the kitchen is a bathtub Yes it's a van Yes that's cool cool
да а кухня это ванна Да это ван
clean everything's cool
Да прикольно прикольно чистенько всё
Yes there is
класс Да есть
water What's that
вода Что там такое
brown thing there
коричневое там
brown there  brown what's
коричневое там коричневое что там
brown down there
коричневое внизу
know what's
зна что
cory then
кори то
turned on what's brown in the bath what's
включил что коричневая в ванне что
brown in the
коричневая в
bath know can you kitchen kitchen Show me
ванне зна а можешь кухню кухню Покажи
kitchen show
кухню
me come on you're a man you're really cool Muk you're really
покажи давай ты мужик ты реально Крутой
cool mo shut up yes shut up
ты Мук ты реально крутой мо молчи да
come on I see I
молчу давай
see in the fridge what products do you have
Вижу вижу в холодильнике что у вас какие
Russians her Russians
продукты россияне ея россияне
eat
едят
cognac from Dagestan from
коньяк из Дагестана из
Dagestan shut up shut up shut
Дагестана молчи молчу молчи
up show
молчи показы
show shut up it's going to
показывай
burn me now
молчи меня сейчас спалит
everything's [ __ ] slept Believe me didn't
вс всё [__] спали Поверь мне не
sleep didn't
спали не
sleep cool cool
спали прикольно прикольно
[music]
[музыка]
sorry it was my call they just called on the
сори это мне звонок просто позвонили по
phone I knocked down my
телефону я сбил
wife didn't wake me up didn't wake me up shut up then Quietly I'll leave now
жену не разбудил же не
to
разбудил молчи то Тихо сейчас уйду ко А
What if she wakes up if
что если она проснётся если
she And if she wakes up EU
она А если она проснётся ЕС
she'll get me Well it can't be it ca
она получу я Да ну не может быть не
n't
может
be because I'm preventing them from sleeping
быть из-за того что я и мешаю спать им
this is
это
who they this is who they this is who I'll get me and who's
кому им это кому им это
there Only sleeping  wife
кому получу я а кто там Спит только жена
or someone else wife or someone else no
или ещё кто-то жена или ещё кто-то нет
wife only and she sleeps separately and she
жена толь а она отдельно спит а она
sleeps separately Yes because I'm
спит Да потому что я
drunk Come on, can you
пьяный Давай можешь мне
show me the light without
показать све свет не
turning it on Well, come on quietly Well, come on
включа Ну давай тихонько Ну давай
quietly so normally we talked so
тихонько так нормально общались так
normally we talked no no no grandfather quietly
нормально общались не не не дед тихонько
through the doors while wife and everything
через двери пока жену и всё
accept that the wife is not an order not a wife
прие что что жена - это не прика не жену
but the room showed said we
а комнату показа сказал мы с тобой
talked well with you and and a balcony Do you have a
хорошо общались а а балкон У тебя есть а
balcony Do you have what balcony Do you have a balcony You have
балкон У тебя есть что балкон У тебя
I didn't understand about the
есть балкон У тебя есть Я не понял по
balcony Do you have a balcony Do you have a balcony Yes and
балкон У тебя есть балкон У тебя есть
why didn't you show the balcony And why did
да а что ты не показал балкон А что ты
n't you show the
не показал
balcony Well I'm interested is it glazed
балкон Ну мне интересно там застеклённый
not glazed because I'm a
не застеклённый потому что я
designer too I just
проектировщик тоже я балконы как раз
design balconies show me well I won't show two balconies I won't
проектируют покажи ну Интере два балкона
go Well it's
пойду Ну он
glazed but it's not crap
застеклённый но не обделался
but look and here are the shoes here are the Russians When
а смотри а вот обувь вот россияне Когда
shoes develop Where they put them right at the
развиваются обувь Где ставят сразу при
entrance or a special cabinet how do you
входе или специальный шкафчик как вы это
arrange it how do you
обустраивает как вы это
arrange it at  there
обустраивать у
is a vestibule at the entrance to our apartment
нас при входе в квартиру есть
how is it a vestibule I know that there is a vestibule
тамбур как это тамбур я знаю что тамбур
in a train And what is a vestibule in an apartment there
в поезде А как это тамбур в квартире там
in the shooting gallery
в тире
wait there is an apartment Here you look at the
подожди есть квартира Вот ты смотришь на
entrance iri on the
подъезд ири на
entrance hung hung
подъезд
such
завис завис такай
Hello Good evening I am from the city of
Здравствуйте Добрый вечер я из города
Khmelnitsky Where are you from
Хмельницкий Вы
Russia the city of Orel Orel Cool And
откуда Россия город орл Орёл Прикольно А
what was it called Orel In honor of
что его назвали Орёл В честь
what in honor of the
чего в честь реки
Orlik River I understood and the river why was it named so the
Орлик понял а реку в чего так
Russian prince drove up to the river and the eagle was hovering just
русский к реке подъехал и орл как раз
above this river Mount Orlik and the river
над этой рекой парил гори Орлик и реч
Orlik was named and then then on this river
Орлик назвали а потом потом на этой реке
in 1161 they built a
в 1161 году поставили
fortress So here the fortress was called Orel
крепость Вот и вот крепость назвали Орёл
and then this Fortress city everything remains
и потом это Крепость город всё оста
cool cool interesting yes it's good
прикольно классно интересно да хорошо
that he didn't see a skunk there
что он там не скунса увидел
Ola
Ола
And a skunk is on the continent on a completely
А скун это на континенте на совсем
different Well, what if some you know from
другом Ну а вдруг какой-то знаете из
overseas they would have brought it from the end they would have released it
заморского привезли бы с конца выпустили
no no that time there was no such communication at
нет нет то время такого общения ещё не
that time America had not yet been discovered at that time
было в то время ещ Америку в то время
America had not yet been discovered on that  same
ещё Америку не открыли сн на том же
con No No look at that time already on that
кон Нет Нет смотрите в то время уже на
Continent Doesh
тот Континент
I meant cola and in the century yes
Доезжаю Я имел в виду колу и в веке да
like it was already True true Vikings
типа это уже было Верно верно Викинги
were already lying so and so True and so not
уже были ври так и есть Так и есть не
only Vikings but also iki and there they already had
только Викинги но ики и там уже у них
Sere Belgo also from the American
Сере бельго тоже с американского
continent They
континента были Это же они друг друга в
went to visit each other easily exactly yes So and you
гости ходили запросто точно да Так а ЧМ
communicate with the World Cup here I don't know It all depends on the
тут общаетесь не знаю Всё зависит от
interlocutors that's what you're interested in And who were
собеседников вот что вам интересно А кто
you by profession while you worked as a livestock
вы по по профессии были пока работали по
breeder
профессии животновод за животными
taking care of animals which ones
ухаживал за какими
exactly For all those that produce products
именно За всеми которые дают продукцию
for humans Well there for Kromi for horses
для человека Ну там за Кромы за лошадьми
for goats
за козами
Absolutely true Absolutely true you're
Совершенно верно Совершенно верно
right you say which ones exactly For
правильно говорите за какими именно За
all that you listed I haven't eaten everything yet well
всеми что вы перечислили Я ещё не все
how well cows goats horses
пере есть ну как ну коровы козы лошади
you named everything correctly that's how it was with
вы назвали правильно всё так и было у
you everything was on the farm everything was right yes yes of
вас всё на ферме всё прямо было да да
course of course Well this is generally a village In
конечно конечно Ну это в общем село В
general the Brigade there is Kolkhoznaya and there everyone
общем Бригада там Колхозная и там всё на
worked on horses They milked the Kings for meat
лошадях работали Корол доили ПКО на мясо
they cut the PKO Well something like that that's all And you
резали Ну как-то так вот и всё А вы
now do you live in a village or in Orel
сейчас живёте в селе или в Орле
I live in a village well in the Oryol region and
Я в селе живу ну в Орловской области а
how far is it from
как далеко от
Orel about 200 km then it is closer to what
орла около 200 км то это ближе к чему
closer to Belarus or where no no no
ближе к Белоруси или куда нет нет нет
no our region is not bordering somewhere
нет у нас моя область не гранична где-то
among I mean in the direction of 200
находится среди име ввиду в сторону 200
km from la In which
км от ла В какую
direction
сторону
Voronezh that is somewhere closer to
Воронежа то есть где-то поближе к
Ukraine it turns out yes yes how to say Well
Украине получается да да как сказать Ну
so to Kursk somewhere 130 km and about the same number of
так до Курска где-то 130 км и примерно
kilometers from Kursk to to
столько же километров от Курска до до
sub And what is the name of the village to me I'm even
суб А как как называется село мне Мне аж
interested I would look on the map
интересно я на карте бы
Yes Look long long
посмотрел Да Посмотрите долгая долгая
long Oryol region yes yes yes yes
долгая Орловская область да дадада да
there you will see there is a long Oryol
там увидите есть долгая Орловская
region I understood And by the way I talk about politics like this
область понял А я кстати так о политике
whose Crimea What do you
общаюсь чей Крым Как вы
think Crimea Crimea
считаете Крым Крым
Crimeans as we say Well what like yes
крымчан как мы говорим Ну что типа да
Crimea Crimeans Dane Donetsk and ki Kievites
Крым крымчан Дане дончан а ки киевлян
hello Just a minute
алло Сейчас минутку
Hello Yes there is Stepan Ugu in short direct
Алло Да есть Степана Угу короче прямые
coordinates y village Dovge
координаты й село довге
e Oryol region yes in  Sumy region
э Орловской области да в Сумской области
198 km as the crow flies you can give me
198 км по прямий можно
the coordinates now I'll
координаты зараз
say so so so
скажу так так так
to 52
до 52
420 1
420 1
Yes there is a command Shlyakh Kalinivka Gremyachka
Да там поруч Шлях калинивка
Grachevka
гремячка Грачевка
on the edge of the Oryol
на краю Орловской
Kursk and Lipetsk
Курской и Липецкой
regions there I am the Ministry of Emergency Situations Ne Dode
области там я МЧС Не Доде
dovgo chi
довго чи
ens Well slo troshki great mo
енс Ну сло трошки великое мо
[music]
[музыка]
Okay accepted Let's call now m called on
Окей принял Давай сейчас м звонил по
business at work and what
делам по работе а что какие-то
interesting objects do you have there Are there
интересные там у вас объекты есть Там
factories or just
заводы или только
farms Well how to say an ordinary village and
фермы Ну как сказать село обыкновенное и
everything is left nothing we had there
всё оста ничего у
agricultural machinery worked there there
на было там сельхозтехника там работали
Transport column then they
там Транспортная колона потом она
say it went bankrupt and in general there is nothing
говорится разорилась и в общем ничего
people live just like that steal cattle
нет народ живёт просто так ворит скотину
And for example I have this where my grandmother
А у меня например вот это где бабушка
lived there was a military unit near the village
жила то там возле села воинская часть
and a missile silo and you
была и Ракетная шахта а у вас какие-то
have some or because you have such a deaf
есть или потому что у вас такой глухой
otl no listen we know how we have this very thing
отл нет слушайте мы знаете как у нас это
only a soldier sees you know when
самое только солдат видим знаете когда
when he comes on vacation from his
когда в отпуск приезжает со свого Может
Maybe so and everything else there yes So
быть так и всё остальное там да Так у
we didn't have any bulls parts there wasn't anyone but it
нас не быки частей никого не было а не
can't be Well really look at the junction of
может быть Ну реально смотрите на стыке
three regions there Lisa You have I
трёх областей там Лиса У вас есть же
see good forests yes Yes no these are forests you
вижу хорошие леса да Да нет это леса
know what it's called in short you can
такие знаете как его короче можно этот
walk this forest somewhere in about
лес пройти где-то минут примерно за
30-40 minutes from end to
30-40 от конца на
end Well look here you have
конец Ну смотрите вот у вас на русановку
good forests on Rusanovka and Grachev there are not
и на Грачёв там леса хорошие есть так не
Rusa Rochok
руса рочок
I know all these villages that you
я все эти сёла знаю которые вы мне
tell me too yes yes they are nearby I am also
говорите тоже да да они рядом Я же тоже
looking yes yes yes yes
смотрю да да дадада да
now military
сейчас воинская
unit this is what district it belongs to
часть это к какому району она относится
this village of
вот эта
yours Yes what village of yours is it
ваша село Да что село ваше это
what is it called so the district is
какая как она называется так район
called the
называется
same name not not long but the
одноимённый не не долгая а
district of
район
Dol
дол
Yes now I will look on Wikipedia It is
Да сейчас я в Википедии посмотрю
very interesting And Dolzhansky district you have
Интересно очень А Должанский район у вас
yes Well yes about long Dolzhansky
да Ну да о долго Должанский
district Well yes just Small I looked on the map
район Ну да просто Маленькая я по карте
I thought small is 3500
посмотрел думал маленькая это 3500
population
населения
if so and there is an administration there is yes Well
если так и есть администрация есть
yes police administration there is well
да Ну да полиция администрация есть ну
actually we have all this as they say
вообще-то у нас всё это как говорится
Here are three districts they are united this is the most
Вот три района они объединены это самое
In general, we have, as they say, many
В общем у нас как говорится много
administrative Such as these have been transferred,
административных Таких вот перенесено
as they say, Here, unite somewhere
как говорится Вот объеди где-то
three or four districts And so on and so forth And here I
три-четыре района И вот так се а вот я
read that, you know, in the village there is a
читаю что знат в посёлке работает
bakery Elevator enterprise Oreon And
хлебзавод Элеватор предприятие Ореон А
what does the
что делает
enterprise do And this is a trading enterprise And what does it
предприятие А это Торговое предприятие А
do there,
что оно там делает
it is there, where Yes, nothing there, there are products there,
он там де Да ничего там продукты там
maybe spare parts for cars, it sells
может быть запчасти для машин продаёт
everything else, there are
всё остальное
spare parts for
там запчасти к
cars Well, approximately Yes, yes, approximately Well, you
машинам Ну примерно Да да да примерно ну
know, like with us, basically, people are
это знаете как у нас в основном люди-то
young people, they generally
в общем молодёжь она в общем по вахте
travel on shifts, they work in other,
ездит вот работает по другим по более
larger cities,
крупным городам
and there is a railway station in the regiment
и в полке находится железнодорожная
It used to work well, but now it does
Раньше она хорошо работала а теперь там
nt work at all, how does it not work, its
вообще о не работает как не работает она
in the direction right here Absolutely
ж по направлению как раз сюда Совершенно
right Absolutely right in the
верно Совершенно верно по
direction Please, please,
направле Дайте раз будь
listen to a correction there, its a district center
ласка слухай поправочка там це райцентр
and there is a zaliznitsa Zaliznitsa it is not
и там зализниця зализниця вона не
used, that is, not for
використовуеться тобто на не якраз не
civilians traveling but for the military  understand that there is
граждански ездя а вийськови нять тобто
little
вона мало
sweat you were licking there susn lku But you
пот ви были зализни там сусн лку Але
see the military are driving here And how
бачишь вони вийськови гоняют сюда А как
often do trains
часто там сейчас поезда у вас
go there now Listen to the passenger Listen
ездят поезда Слушай пассажирских Слушай
there is one little train going there that's the most well how is
ездит там один паровозик это самое ну
it like in general like a bus two
как он типа как в общем как автобус два
little cars are driving back and forth and that's it and the freight ones
Вагончика туда-сюда гоняет и всё оста а
are going but not
грузовые ездят же да не
bad at the elevator dot for grain and the Armed Forces and the
убо ком элеватора дот за зерном и ВС а
freight ones in short listen on asking
грузовых никах короче слухай на прося
climbed in too it
залез
seems to you nothing to go like there is
тоже каже ти ничего не ездить типа там
some kind of car but it seems muddy to me
вагончик какой-то да Але мутный мне
I am sulfur
сдается я серно
rolling th lki car like there are two
катить ть льки вагончик типа там бля два
Tuziks in short there are a couple of people there I
Тузика короче там пару людей дить я то
say the lka is thrown that is tho just
кажу закинута лка то есть вони якраз
through Orel not going through where many of our
через орл не ганя через де багато наших
people like maybe they can make a video about the
людей типа можуть зняти видос про
transfer but tho such small
переброску а вони такими маленькими
villages small tho tho
сёлами маленькими вони нять
equipment and  there is some bridge Do you
технику а там мост какой-то У вас
have a railway
есть Железнодорожный
but not a
а не
railway Look at this so that you
нету слу я смотри вот это чтоб было
understand This is the road This road is
поняти Вот это дорога вот эта дорога она
not even
даже не
electrified It runs diesel I
электрифицировано вот дизеля гоняет я
understand
понял
Yes, it's
да еруда
just nonsense PPP This is a railroad It goes through
просто ППП это железка она идт через
Shlyakh It goes from Shlyakh to Dolgoye And from
Шлях Она со шляха идт в долгое А с
Dolgoye from Dolgoye it goes there all the way to
долгого с долгого идёт вово туда аж на
Vorontsov
Воронцов
Yes What kind of Vorontsovka I don't know such a
да ко Что за Воронцовка не знаю такой
Vorontsovka Well there it is already to the
воронцовки ну туда на это уже на
neighboring region In short it E Your
соседнюю область Короче она Э Ваш э
city enters and this is already in the Kursk
город заходит а это уже в Курской
region Yes it enters Dolgoye from Shlyakh
области Да она в долгое со шляха заходит
Yes railroads from the side
Да железные дороги со стороны
this No no this is said as a kind of
это Нет нет это это говорится как типа
suburb Yes in general it is a village somewhere about one and a
пригорода Да в общем это посёлок где-то
half kilometers Yes yes well this Shlyakh
километра полтора Да да ну этот Шлях
like yes that is it is from there the
типа да то есть это ээ оттуда заходит
railroad enters so before that it goes
дорога железная так перед этим она идёт
goes Damn how well on the maps of these
идёт блин как хорошо на картах этих
satellites it is visible from Studyonny Yes It
спутников видно из студёного да
turns out the railroad goes through Studyonny
Получается через студёный проходит
Yes yes yes yes yes Everything is
железная дорога да дадада дада да Всё
cool Yes yes I understand by And it turns out  a
круто Дада понятно по а получается а
stop stop and from the long one it already goes to the
стоп стоп а с долгого выходит уже на
Kursk region from you Yes yes absolutely
курскую область от вас Да да совершенно
probably and somewhere there is some river
наверно а где-то речечка какая-то есть
because it is not visible well on the maps I do not see a river river
потому что плохо видно на картах не вижу
look we have this well exactly so that the
смотри у нас это ну именно чтобы
railway can pass through the river
железная дорога через речечка проходить
so that there is a bridge but no such thing there is no
чтобы мостик был есть а нет такого тако
such thing no no no Look how there
такого нету нету нету Вот смотри как не
cannot be at least some small
может быть хотя бы небольшой какой-то
bridge I am telling you I am telling you I am telling you I have a
мостик я рассказываю я рассказываю я
grandfather Come back you have a call I
дедушка Возвращайтесь у вас звонок я
know Don't run away I need a river
знаю Вы не убегайте Мне нужно речечка
find the locale Zro on the
найти локали Зро на
map grandfather Come on turn off the call
карте дед Давай отключай звонок
Come back here
Возвращайся сюда
okay
ладно
Hello And to you too Hello I am
Здравствуйте И вам тоже Здравствуйте я
from the city of Khmelnitsky
из города Хмельницкий Вы
where are you from I am from the city of
откуда Я из города
Krasnodar the country is Russia I understood top is far from you
Краснодар страна Россия понял топ от вас
well 150 km there Yesterday it seems
далеко ну 150 км там Вчера вроде в топса
Ukrainian drones flew into topsa they
прилетали украинские беспилотники привет
sent greetings And to you too hello Ivan
передавали И вам тоже привет Иван
Ivan seriously You know
Иван серьёзно Ты знаешь
me friend
меня друг
bro you know me
бра ты знаешь меня
yes My name is Maxim Maxim understood I
да Меня Максим зовут Максим понял я тебя
confused you with Ivan and how do you communicate in
спутал с Иван а чём общаешься ты вчт
roulette Well I don't know  me the last
рулетке Ну не знаю у меня последний
Challenge send 15 Ukrainian
Челлендж послать 15 украинских
opponents because they do not respect the
оппонентов потому что они не уважают
conversation with me They interrupt they mince
разговор со мной Они перебивают они мят
stick to their line and do not want to listen to
гнут свою линию и не хотят слушать
anyone It irritates me very much
никого Меня это очень сильно раздражает
and that's why I send And I communicate normally
и поэтому я шлю А я я нормально общаюсь
with
с
Russians Well, excuse me,
русскими Ну извини
come on, look, you have at home,
ты давай смотри вот у тебя есть дома
for example, a book called
например книжка
Ostrava There really is Yes, you're kidding,
остра есть реально Да ты прикалываешься
show me, I randomly named the book Well, there is,
покажи я я наугад назвал книгу Ну есть
show me, it's a damn miracle, I randomly
покажи я это блин Чудо я случайную книгу
named a book, you say there is, I don't
назвал ты говоришь есть не
believe it, not somewhere, my pictures slip through
верю не где-то мои снимки проскальзывать
Well, there
ну
really is Max Damn Max, you're a
реально есть Макс Блин Макс ты это
miracle By the way, yes, you know, here you are, you
чудо Кстати да ты знаешь вот ты мне ты
remind me of you By the way, your face is such a
мне напомни у тебя Вот кстати лицо такое
Cossack, as a child I read a fairy tale
казацкое вот я в детстве читал сказку
about the Cossack Golota, there were pictures there,
про казака голоту вот там было картинки
just like
вот прямо как
you Well, this is my relative Yes,
ты Ну это родствен мои Да родственник
your relative was the Cossack
твой был казак
Golota
голота
Yes, seriously Well, at least by the last name I
Да серьёзно Ну по крайней мере по фами
understood that you are Max
понял то ты Макс
Golota Yes, a Cossack Yes, I
голота Да казак Да
understood, this is cool Damn, you see something here,
понял это кайф Блин видишь тут что-то
fate sent me straight to you I
меня прямо послала к тебе судьба я
somehow guessed about Ostrava Here  accidentally
как-то угадал про остро Вот случайно мне
came to me sharp and then Gop you change hold
пришла остр и тут Гоп ты изменя держи
there Rossi is
Там Росси
doing for you understood Well I don't lie you
за тебя делает понял Ну я не дежу ты
seem to be like well smart person or Well there is a little bit of
вроде как бы ну умный человек или Ну
that Yes there is a little bit of that And I would like to
чуть есть такое Да чуть есть да А хотел
increase my level of
бы увеличить уровень своего
intelligence Well I would like to yes Let's conduct I can conduct
интеллекта Ну хотел бы да Давай проведём
Let's not conduct a
могу провести Давай не будем проводить
survey And you just tell me about something
опрос А ты мне просто о чём-нибудь
yes I can conduct a ritual about
расскажешь да я могу провести обряд о
increasing intelligence
прибавлении
such a shaman topic
ума такую шаманку тему
I something about history Tell me can you
я что-нибудь про историю Скажи можешь
Look I really take a book in my hands I'll
Смотри я реально возьми книгу в руки Я
tell you about history take some book
про историю расскажу возьми книгу
in your
какую-то в
hands some kind of smart Well here's the
руки какую-то да умную Ну вот самую
smartest book in your house
умную книгу в своём доме
Find it like this Okay you can stand in front of
Найди так О'кей можешь встать перед
the mirror I can but you won't see me Well
зеркалом могу но ты меня не увидишь Ну
no let's in front we'll conduct a ritual about
нет давай перед мы проведём обряд по
increasing
увеличению
intelligence come on ok come on I'm throwing it on
ума давай хорошо давай я подкидывают на
such Generally rare
такую Вообще редко
Come on I'm in front of the mirror so take the phone in front of me
Давай я пере зеркал так возьми телефон
She's in front of me so take the
пере с собой Она передо мной так возьми
phone so I can
телефон чтобы я тебя
see you No I can't Speak ok I'm Maxim
видел Нет не могу Хорошо говори Я Максим
Golota I'm okay Come on return the change
голота Я те ладно Давай возвращай сда
near the refrigerator we'll conduct a
возле холодильника проведём
ritual so it's also conducted in front of That's
обряд так он же проводится
all Let's do it then  let's spend it in
пере Всё Давайте тогда проведём перед
front of the
этим перед
refrigerator Come on in front of the refrigerator
холодильником Давай перед холодильником
take a book a book to your heart Apply
возьми книгу книгу к сердцу Приложи
Yes say
Да говори
I'm Maximus
я я Максимус
naked Well Maximus is a big word
голота Ну Максимус это громко сказано
just Maxim Okay Maxim naked yes I'll
просто Максим Хорошо Максим голо да
say 22 years
скажу 22 года
old 32 years old 32
отроду 32 года 32
years old I ask the universe I ask the universe to
года прошу вселенную прошу вселенную
add to my
прибавить мне
mind add to my mind so that I would be
ума прибавить мне ума чтоб был я
wise so that I would be wise so that I would be watch
мудрым чтобы я мудрым чтоб был я
dedicated so that I would receive the
просм посвящённом чтоб получил я пре
Nobel Prize Well he
премию Нобелевскую
knows that Okay let me get
Ну это знает Ну ладно пускай я получу
more you ask the universe more it will give okay I promise I
при больше просишь у вселенной больше
promise to read books read books
обязуюсь читать книги читать книги
every evening
каждый вечер
M Okay no say every evening every
М ну ладно нет скажи каждый вечер каждый
evening at least one page
вечер хотя бы по одной странице
at least one
хотя бы по одной
page I ask the universe I ask the universe to
странице прошу вселенную прошу вселенную
betray me my desires betray me my
предать мне мои желания предать мне мои
desires now Open the book to
желания теперь Открой книгу на седьмой
page seven and read the seventh line from
странице и прочитай седьмую строчку
the top if there aren't a
сверху если тут не стоко
hundred Let's count together
тки Давай считать вме
Let's
Давай
two
два
three four there should be
3 четыре там внизу должно быть написано
seven written below at the bottom the number seven if there is this is the
семь внизу цифра семь если есть это
seventh page Yes  no I therefore
седьмая страница Да нету Я поэтому
counted manually Okay 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 and
вручную считал Ладно 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 и
through a straw
сквозь трубочку
you can through a straw you can See even
можно сквозь трубочку можно Видишь даже
uh to us the Universe go that even through a
э нам Вселенная го что даже сквозь
straw you can get drunk with new knowledge
трубочку можно напиться новыми знаниями
from the
из
Universe You have such where they
Вселенной У вас такие где
grow I understand Listen Max But imagine such a
растят понял Слушай Макс А вот прикинь
situation
такая ситуация
uh you are
ээ ты
standing next to the corpse of Ivan the Fool for example
стоишь рядом труп Ивана дурака например
some kind of yes there is a grenade Dava lie down
какого-то да тут граната Дава лежи
normally please
нормально пожалуйста
and Putin what will you do and Putin is standing
и Путин что ты сделаешь а Путин стоит
or lying Putin is standing Putin is standing Hello
или лежит Путин стоит Путин стоит Привет
Volodya mo
волод мо
poch A grenade A grenade What kind of grenade I
поч А граната А граната Какая граната
understood well Yes by the way And look also you
понял хорошо Да кстати А смотрите ещё
know there is also such a technique about
знаете ещё есть такая техника о
adding intelligence by changing the diet can you
прибавлении ума изменением диеты можете
show what you eat I will tell you for
показать чем вы питаетесь я подскажу
example Which foods maybe you shouldn't
например Какие продукты может не стоит
eat and which ones Maybe on the contrary you should eat more yes
есть а какие Может наоборот больше есть
for the development of the mind Show
да для развития ума Покажите
the refrigerator what is it I only
холодильник что это я только семенами
eat seeds not And really in the refrigerator What
питаюсь не А реально в холодильнике Что
Show nothing empty Well Open what is
Покажите ничего пустой Да ну Откройте
really empty I don't believe Yes empty
что реально пустой я не верю Да пустой
Yes I really don't believe Open
Да реально не верю
Avet so empty And why do you
Авет так пусто А зачем же ты его
keep it on Let it
держишь Пускай
work cool I turned it on so that it
работает прикольно Я же его включил для
worked Let it
того чтобы он работал Пускай
work interesting No need do you live alone
работает интересно Не надо ты живёшь сам
or with someone alone Well yes and do you
или с кем-то один один Ну да а и семена
eat these seeds yes yes
вот эти ешь да да галлюциногенные
some kind of hallucinogenic seeds no ordinary ordinary
какие-то семена нет обычные обычные
seeds Yes and what kind of plants seeds of
семена Да а что за растения семена
what
какого
plant
растения
parsley dill
петрушка укроп
cilantro Can you Let's do a
кинза А можешь Давай сделаем обряд
cilantro eating ritual Show how real I've
поедания кинзы Покажи как реально Я
never seen people eat
никогда не видел как люди едят
cilantro Well I don't want to now I'm not allowed after
кинзу Ну я сейчас не хочу мне после
six You can't eat
шести
seeds after six yes I
Нельзя Нельзя семена есть после шести да
understand And did you read the fairy tale about the Cossack
понял А ты читал сказку про казака
Golota tale Yes I read it but it was A long time ago
голоту сказ Да читал но это было Давно
it was about a girl can you tell me
это было лет дев можешь мне рассказать
about this fairy tale
про эту сказку
No I don't remember anymore I don't
Нет не помню уже не
remember understood And what did this Cossack Golota do
помню понял А что этот казак голота
I don't remember how I'll tell you understood well
делал я не помню как я тебе скажу понял
how would you like well come on he gave you in short
ну как бы ну давай тебе он короче
first to Garik Kharlamov Then he
сначала гарику Харламову дал Потом
came to Pavel Volya st he had a car and
пришёл К Павлу Воле ул у него машину а
then
затем
Nate the
Нате
ointment
мази
understood told you
понял тебе рассказывал
this question Why in Russian folk
се вопрос Почему в русских народных
tales the hero is always Ivan the
сказках герой всегда Иван
Fool Well because he goes for
дурак Ну потому что он идёт на
broke how is it for broke That's how it is
пролом как это на пролом
like There is such a
Вот так это типа Есть такая
proverb smart  you won't go up the mountain
пословица умный в гору не пойдёт
continue because it's New
продолжишь потому что Новый
Year There's
год
no equal right
Нет ровня пра
deeds So why is Ivan the Fool in
дела Так а почему Иван дурак в
fairy tales because we're not all
сказках потому что мы не все ошибка
smart mistake Can you bring some book
умны А можешь е какую-то книгу принести
tomorrow there's a book Okay come on now
вотре есть книга Хорошо давай сейчас
you come on you're
ты
pregnant what to
беременный что
do howl
делать выть
mop wab Come on let's
швабру ваб Давай давай
do it she doesn't listen to me Let's
сделаем она не слушает меня Давай
do a ritual Yes so that you don't get
сделаем обряд Да так чтобы ты не
pregnant I won't be able to do it
забеременел я не смогу этого сделать
physically if m
физически если м
in short no Kadyrovets didn't
короче никакой кадыровец не это не
try to get pregnant let's do a ritual Yes
попробовал забеременеть сделаем обряд Да
With pleasure And there are Kadyrovets
С удовольствием А есть кадыровцы
normally you want a Kadyrovets to
нормально ты хочешь чтобы кадыровец
do a ritual with you Well let them do it
сделал с тобой обряд Ну пускай сделат
this way if I get pregnant I'll give you a million
так если я забеременею я тебе миллион
dollars Yes Listen I'm ready even without a million
долларов даю Да Слушай я и без миллиона
dollars for a
долларов готов чтобы тебя просто
Kadyrovets to simply take away the
кадыровец отберет
essence of your thoughts I understand
суть твоих мыслей я понял
okay Come
ладно Давай
on I'm just
продолжай мне просто
interested interesting
интересно интересно
come on me this is a
давай меня
lamp that will accompany
это лампа которая будет сопровождать
me all my life this is a lamp that gives me
меня всю жизнь это лампа которая даёт
its power it gives me the power of fire and
мне свою силу она даёт мне силу огня а
I also
также я
want Well in my opinion everything is finished the ritual
хочу Ну по-моему всё обряд закончил
Come on  let's do the
Давай проведём
ritual Let's maybe we should but we need to in front of the
обряд Давай може надо но нужно перед
mirror Get up in front of the mirror
зеркалом Вставай перед зеркалом
I stood in front of it take it not with a phone with a
я стоял перед возьми не с телефоном с
camera so that I could also see the mirror I
камерой чтобы я тоже видел зеркало я не
can't why Well because it doesn't
могу почему Ну потому что так Не катит
work Why doesn't it work the phone only works
Почему не катит телефон работает только
on charge And once and a mirror Bring it
на зарядке А раз а зеркало Принеси тогда
here then And what else should I do
сюда А ещё мне что сделать бетон
disassemble the concrete maybe stuff the cat with
разобрать может быть кошку нафаршировать
pepper what can't I do with it What's
перцем что мне её сделать не могу Что
not clear
непонятного
take the phone to the mirror how much charge do
возьми телефон к зеркалу сколько зарядки
you have
у тебя
now
сейчас
1%
1%
show show show what about
покажи показать показать что о про
Show okay
Покажи ладно
about the
о
process Tell me where you got a book about
проце Скажи откуда у тебя книга про
pregnancy because I was pregnant
беременность потому что я был беременным
but I had a miscarriage I almost
но у меня случился выкидыш Я почти
made a million dollars I thought that
заработал миллион долларов я думал что
you were a
ты есть
miscarriage
выкидыш
Well if I were a miscarriage I would have died but
Ну если бы я был выкидышем я бы умер а
here I'm not And prove that you're
тут нет А докажи что ты
alive Maybe you're a
живой Может ты
zombie
Зомби
what
что
yes Well I
да Ну я
understand to me what Show look Take Take water like this
понимаю мне что Покажи смотри Возьми
and show that the water
Возьми так воду и покажи что вода на
runs off your hands the zombie's water is
твоих руках стекает у зомби вода
absorbed
впитывается
into the
в
skin let's
шкуру давай
show how much that
покажу насколько что
I Let's have a fight I'll water myself let's have
я Давай сеча себ полью давай
fun le  Well, you need to Heat up the water
ради прикола ле Ну надо Подогрей воду
like what to heat up the water so that the temperature is not
как что подогреть воду чтоб температу не
room Okay, come on, pour it soaks in
комнат Ладно давай лей
Where in the sweater Yes, in the hand, no, show me there is water on the hand, it has
впитывается Куда в кофту
soaked in, it has soaked in Where is all the Water that
впиталась она впиталась Где вся Вода
you poured out Here it is soaked in,
которую ты вылил Вот она впитывается
look, pour it on your hand and I look to those,
смотри лей на руку и я смотрю дотех если
if to those, then it is not soaked in If to the sweater,
дотех значит не впитывается Если до
here pour it on the dol, you need to pour it out yes Well, more, more, pour
кофты вот лей на доло душку надо
more, more, no So you poured a little
больше больше ле нет Так ты мало налила
but it will not soak in more so that we can see whether it is
но не впитается больше чтобы мы видели
soaked in or not, pour more,
впитывается или нет налей
some x, more, pour some
больше какой-то х больше налей
water, came in, well, you are really talking I
воды какой-то зашёл ну реально несёшь Я
thought at least something, at least Come on,
думал хоть что-нибудь хотя бы Давай
Let's
Давай нормально поговорим давай
talk normally, let's talk normally, out of eight, at least
нормально поговори из восьми хотя бы
something will
хоть что-нибудь
burn out Complete zero, what kind of magician are you, go put
выгореть Полный ноль какой ты маг иди
this candle, take it,
свечку вот эту
look at the fields on
постави возьми смотри полей на ты на
which hand you poured, the right or the
какую руку лил правую или
left I look at which hand, the right or the left,
левую Я на какую руку на правую или на
you poured, poured, held,
левую смотрю ты лел лил на левую держал
But it should be the other way around so that  pour on the right
А надо наоборот чтобы на правую лить
take the kettle in your left hand and pour on the
возьми чайник в левую руку и полей на
right Show that the right hand does not
правую Покажи что правая рука не
Absorb water that you are not a Zombie
Впитывает в себя воду что ты не Зомби
This is the
Это
left What does the left or the
левая Причём тут левая или
right have to do with it Show that the
правая Покажи что вторая рука Покажи что
second hand does not Absorb water Sowing water flows that
вторая рука не воду Сея стекает вода что
you are not a Zombie Show
ты не Зомби
please
Покажи пожалуста
and let's talk
и поговорим
normally we can talk
нормально мы сейчас можем говорить
normally now No I'm afraid that you are a
нормально Нет я я боюсь что ты
Zombie you don't have a refrigerator you are
Зомби холодильника нет у тебя это
suspicious you don't eat you are a Zombie
подозрительно ты не ешь ты Зомби
maybe Show that the water in the second hand does
возможно Покажи что во вторую руку вода
not
не
Absorb
Впитывает
Oh threw it up
Ой подкидывал ну
okay more more Pour don't feel sorry don't feel
ладно больше больше Лей не жалей
sorry you will wash the floor for me squeeze you
не жалей ты мне пол мыть будешь сжи ты
threw the water you threw
скинул воду ты сбросил
it closer to the camera
её ближе к камере
where you have to And where you have to
где придётся А где
somewhere you have to where you have to
приходится где-то приходится то где тебе
eat Well not at home what What do
приходится питаться Ну не дома что Чем
you eat not at
ты питаешься не
home well
дома ну
the day before yesterday Pose the day before yesterday ate I
позавчера Поза позавчера ел
understood well You vote for Putin it seems at
понял ну Ты за Путина голосуешь походу
least you have something smart you see such a
да хоть что-то у тебя умное видишь такое
feeling that someone performed a ritual on you
ощущение что над тобой кто-то провёл
I am you a
обряд я тебя
Zombie You should should take and to all the
Зомби Ты должен должен взять и всем
neighbors  say Putin three times
соседям сказать Путин трижды с балкона
go out from the balcony n Putin
выйти н Путин
Putin this is unreal
Путин це нереальный
dya write on y Instagram I don't know
дя пись на й Instagram Я не знаю для
why this is for you why else you should watch
чого це тоб для чого ще тоб там дивитись
on my face But for you this is one
на оцей мий фейс Але для тебе це один
two or three clicks But you try me and I
два або три клика Але ты тримае мене и я
will say you in me there are a bunch of fouls and in
буду каза ва в мене там Купа фолов и в
me there will be a cool mood to do but
мене буде класный настрий щоб робити но
cool video write on y Instagram popk
крут вдео пись на й Instagram попк
Andriy that's it
Андрий вот
come on I'm waiting for you
так давай я тебя чекаю